<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning Equations</title>
    <description>ah!</description>
    <link>http://www-users.cs.umn.edu/~verma//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www-users.cs.umn.edu/~verma//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 20:53:20 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 20:53:20 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reading List: ICML Papers 2016 </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ll be providing my comments, may be some quick or sometime detail, on  the papers which I find interesting and related to my research area. Hopefully, this will come handy in solving my own research problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starting with ICML 2016 Papers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Revisiting Semi-Supervised Learning with Graph Embeddings ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Why Regularized Auto-Encoders learn  Sparse Representation? ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the Consistency of Feature Selection With Lasso for Non-linear Targets. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Additive Approximations in High Dimensional Nonparametric Regression via the SALSA. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Variational Nystrom method for large-scale spectral problems. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A Kernelized Stein Discrepancy for Goodness-of-fit Tests and Model Evaluation. ICML 2016 (Possibly a new way to measure difference in probability distribution other than most common – KL divergence )&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Low-Rank Matrix Approximation with Stability. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unsupervised Deep Embedding for Clustering Analysis. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Online Low-Rank Subspace Clustering by Explicit Basis Modeling. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Community Recovery in Graphs with Locality. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Analysis of Deep Neural Networks with Extended Data Jacobian Matrix. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stochastic Variance Reduced Optimization for Nonconvex Sparse Learning. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compressive Spectral Clustering ICML. 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Variance-Reduced and Projection-Free Stochastic Optimization. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learning Convolutional Neural Networks for Graphs. ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discrete Deep Feature Extraction: A Theory and New Architectures.  ICML 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 17:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www-users.cs.umn.edu/~verma//paperlist/2016/05/29/ReadingListICML16.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www-users.cs.umn.edu/~verma//paperlist/2016/05/29/ReadingListICML16.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>PaperList</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
